In the affliction, in the night
In the questions I can’t fight
You are sovereign, You are near
Even when I’m crushed by fear
When the losses take their toll
And there’s sorrow in my soul
I will lift my hands and sing
You are worthy, You are King
Through the trial, through the test
You reveal Yourself and give me rest
I had heard of You before
Now my eyes have seen the Lord
You laid the earth’s foundation
Made the stars in their formation
Who am I to doubt Your grace?
You are perfect in Your ways
You have bound the cords of light
You command the seas at night
Still You hear my faintest cry
You will lift my head on high
Through the trial, through the test
You reveal Yourself and give me rest
I had heard of You before
Now my eyes have seen the Lord
You are holy, You are wise
You are Lord of earth and skies
Though I suffer, I have peace
For your mercies never cease
You are holy, You are wise
You are Lord of earth and skies
Though I suffer, I have peace
For your mercies never cease
Through the trial, through the test
You reveal Yourself and give me rest
I had heard of You before
Now my eyes have seen the Lord
Now my eyes… have seen the Lord